pdfconvertonline.com 2018-01-01

# Privacy Policy

PDFConvertOnline.com is dedicated to making your online experience as interesting and enjoyable as possible. We truly appreciate your presence on our site and at all times understand that you are our guest and should be treated accordingly. To ensure this, we have listed the components of our Privacy Policy below.

**Use of Personal Information**  
Any information you submit through PDFConvertOnline.com will be held in the strictest confidence. In no way will your personal information ever be used without your consent. To ensure this, all forms on our web sites that send information to a database that may be used in the future, e.g. mailing lists, registration, etc., have check boxes where you specify whether or not you would like to receive information from us in the future. Forms used just to send email, post messages, etc., do not include the option, but will never be used to send information. Be assured that we do not sell our name and address lists. If you choose to receive information from us, each message will also include instructions on how to "unsubscribe" from future mailings should you wish to cancel.

The only information we automatically collect is that related to the use of our web site. This information is anonymous and is gathered through our servers' log files. These log files record generic information, such as the number of visits our web site receives, the types of browsers used and the number of files downloaded, but never personal information. This log file information allows us to create better content aimed at our viewer's preferences.

**Security**  
We use industry-standard efforts to safeguard the confidentiality of your transmissions (as well as your personally identifiable information), including firewalls and one-way hash encryption technology. These are the same technologies that most websites use to safeguard credit card information and other personal information. While we make every effort to ensure that your information is secure on our system, no data transmission over the Internet can be guaranteed to be 100% secure. As a result, we cannot guarantee the security of any information you transmit to us, and you do so at your own risk. We will continue to enhance our security procedures as new technology becomes available. We recommend that you do not divulge your password to anyone.

**Use of Cookies**  
Some of our pages use a feature of your browser called a "cookie." Cookies, by themselves, are not able to extract any personal information from you. This cookie automatically identifies your computer - but not you - to our servers when you visit our site. Unless you specifically tell us, PDFConvertOnline.com will never know who you are, even though we may assign your computer a cookie. Also, PDFConvertOnline.com can only read cookies created by PDFConvertOnline.com. Cookies allow us to personalize our site for you and to provide you with information that fits your needs and desires. For instance, once you register your product online, a cookie is written to your computer so that you will not need to type information in the future to obtain support.

**Questions or Comments**  
PDFConvertOnline.com knows that your privacy is very important to you. We welcome questions and comments regarding this policy, so feel free to contact us. Because technologies on the Internet change so quickly, PDFConvertOnline.com reserves the right to modify its Privacy Statement from time to time.
